Kostadis Roussos: Hello, Nikhil.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hello.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, no.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Sorry, I switched my monitor, I need to.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, it should work.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you get a new PC?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Can you hear me?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I can, I can.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: One second, I need to… Switch to a bigger wallet?
Kostadis Roussos: I always find it funny who clicks on my licks.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What's that?
Kostadis Roussos: I always find it amusing, What, what?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Dueprint.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm going to switch something matters.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Click on the audio link if you want to hear audio music right now.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I did.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, it's not supported on Safari.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Wait, why can't I click the… Sergeant's cabling.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm accepting the privacy, okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Meanwhile…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, I can't click anything on that later.
Kostadis Roussos: You can't?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, you shouldn't be able to… you shouldn't be able… let me just see something. You should hear something.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, yeah, yeah, now all the…
Kostadis Roussos: It's not about you clicking, I just needed…
Kostadis Roussos: If you, if you can… the webpage can come up, and you heard the sounds, then we're good.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: App Syrinscape.com, I can see some controls.
Kostadis Roussos: But, no, that's fine.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: coffee.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you just… this is…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, you can try playing some sound now.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I don't ju… did you hear that?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Can you hear something that I'm doing?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I can.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I don't know how to spell it.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, is it you're hearing music from me, or is it from me?
Kostadis Roussos: from me.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, I mean, yeah, from my background.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: From this website.
Kostadis Roussos: It should have stopped now.
Kostadis Roussos: I think what happened was I started playing a sound.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, it's stopped now.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, perfect document.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me search.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I'm just kidding about that.
Kostadis Roussos: A second, they need to just do one thing.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'll be right back.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: I think I got everything. I think I am good now.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, always kind of funny to see what the world thinks.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Always fascinating to see how technology works.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What did you discover?
Kostadis Roussos: Nothing, nothing… I mean, okay, so…
Kostadis Roussos: What did I discover? Discovered a great many things.
Kostadis Roussos: But one of the things I discovered is that…
Kostadis Roussos: Fucking using these models is a lot more complicated than you think it is.
Kostadis Roussos: Models? Okay, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, getting useful…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: It's complicated to get to do what you want, actually.
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, no. That's not actually what I was talking about. Never mind that. So let me say, I agree with you.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So let's say… so let me start off with 100% agree.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, no disagreement.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, just getting them to work.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, if you're trying to run them and get them to work efficiently and take efficient use of your hardware, holy fuck is their… are they complicated?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay, I get it, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm like, I'm not… all the things you said? Completely agreed.
Kostadis Roussos: Thumbs up!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What platform are you using to run?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, let me give me a second, let me do something. I just…
Kostadis Roussos: So I have these two DGX Sparks.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, over here. And… They're,
Kostadis Roussos: So it's, NVIDIA, sort of a supercomputer in a box kind of thing?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, yes, I recently heard about it.
Kostadis Roussos: 128GB of, unified RAM.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm trying to configure these things to get good perf… it's like, like, learning how to use their performance is tricky, because, like.
Kostadis Roussos: they're… Per token output is actually low, but their throughput is pretty high.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Like, the number of tokens it's using for the context?
Kostadis Roussos: So, the number of con- so the number of tokens it can generate It's quite low.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh yeah, but a lot of tokens get used, like, between the layers, I suppose.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, it's just the performance of the memory bandwidth is so piss-poor.
Kostadis Roussos: That it could only generate about 20 tokens per second.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right? Oh, that's pretty low, actually, 22%.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: The baker.
Kostadis Roussos: But if you use, like, but if you use naive models naively.
Kostadis Roussos: So, if you use the right models and the right ways and the right techniques, you can actually get
Kostadis Roussos: Recently, like, you could get up to, like, 200 tokens per second throughput.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, wow, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: But not on any single prompt.
Kostadis Roussos: So you can get really high throughput, but very poor latency.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I see, okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And so…
Kostadis Roussos: That's for some models. Other models, you can get pretty high throughput, latency, and very fast tokens, but poor reasoning. And then other models, you can get, like, it's just…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Are you okay?
Kostadis Roussos: And then it's like, well, if you use this feature and that feature and combine it with that model and that model, you could get this, but, like…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: But yeah, I mean, like, having 128 or 120GB of unified RAM, I think you can run larger models.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, you can run larger models, but, like, there's a qualitative difference between the 80 billion parameter one and the 122 billion parameter one.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah, yeah. There must be, like, significant difference.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I didn't really believe that until I tried it.
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: How did you actually confirm that, with the same prompt? Input prompt, like you gave.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, no, I mean, like, I had a programming task.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I had a programming task where I wanted it to convert some
Kostadis Roussos: To, to read some webpages.
Kostadis Roussos: And convert it, and convert… read some poorly done WordPress stuff… WordPress stuff. Oh!
Kostadis Roussos: Actually… for you.
Kostadis Roussos: I forgot. Part of the reason I did this was to make your life easier.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Are you exposing the DGIC Spark compute via some API that I can use?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Are you exposing the DGX Spark compute via.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, I'm actually doing something more useful.
Kostadis Roussos: I got really annoyed with the UI, the webpage.
Kostadis Roussos: So, if you download this webpage.
Kostadis Roussos: I put the link in there.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. If you download this webpage and load it into your browser, you'll get a useful version of the RPG Builder for, Druids.
Kostadis Roussos: For rogues.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: The ropes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, if I open this in the browser, you mean.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, and download the page, download the HTML, and then open the page, the HTML in a web browser. I couldn't be bothered to set up a web server.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep, yep.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Divine Domain. Soul-like, arcane Trickster, assassin, thief.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Species…
Kostadis Roussos: Cheers.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I can see. Rogue Builder. I've downloaded the Rogue Builder.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Wizard spends, other critics pens.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: teeth.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: If he's halfling.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, this is pretty cool.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: This webpage is cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, I just got very annoyed with the webpage that the guy had put together, which was, like, then he had inflicted it with more ads to the point where it was causing my computer to crash.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, the RPG bot, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, it was just awful, and so I was like, fuck this shit. I'm just gonna, like, go create a webpage. And so, I tried to send the small model, and the small model choked at what I thought was a fairly straightforward exercise.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: And then…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: When you say a small model, like, how small?
Kostadis Roussos: The 80 billion parameter one.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Then the 120, actually…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, the 122 one actually was able to… actually, to be fair, the 81 was able to get… the coder model was able to produce this webpage, but it was only able to produce this webpage. When I gave it other webpages, it started getting confused and hopelessly meandering.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: And so, the thing that I real… the problem… so there are a couple of interesting things that happened. One was…
Kostadis Roussos: The damn thing always wants to use regex instead of parsing the HTML properly.
Kostadis Roussos: So I had to give… I had to tell it to create a prompt to tell it to never do that again.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Never use regex.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, when you're parsing HTML, use a parser, dammit!
Kostadis Roussos: Then there were some other tricky things around, like, the 80 billion parameter one kind of kept, like, it kept requiring a lot more babysitting than I would have liked. The 122 one required a modest, a very tiny bit of babysitting, and then it was off to the races.
Kostadis Roussos: So, like, the 2022 one was actually, okay, this one I could use.
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm. For this kind of work.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Got it, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And so, like, if I'm needing to write… if I'm needing to write any kind of script or webpage or tool like this.
Kostadis Roussos: I wouldn't, I mean, like, I would use the 122 model. And then, for some of the things I do with Claude, I now found that the 128 one actually works just fine for my purposes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: I accidentally tried it out, and so…
Kostadis Roussos: The problem I was running into was its latency was shit… shitty, well, the token per second was pretty low, and I'm like, when I got, like.
Kostadis Roussos: $10,000 worth of hardware to get 20 tokens per second? That's kind of lame.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And then I… so then I… so then it turned out, like, I had to do a whole bunch of fucking research on, you know, how to use this better, and, like, I had to, like, you know, I had to learn about…
Kostadis Roussos: The concept of…
Kostadis Roussos: What you want to do is you want to shove… you want to do as much pre-fill as you can, so that the decode happens in power… that you get a lot more decode happening.
Kostadis Roussos: And so the decode phase is when it generates the tokens, right? And so that, like, took me a while to figure out. And then I had to figure out that there's all sorts of, like, interesting behaviors about how VLLM works.
Kostadis Roussos: And how it consumes memory, and how Ray consumes memory?
Kostadis Roussos: Right, and s…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's like digging very deep, I mean, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, I mean, like, I'm telling you, right? Like, like… Because it kept crashing.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: It's like going multiple layers down.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I know, I'm just trying to say, like, I'm, like, I, like, yeah, yeah, getting this thing to actually work was, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Fuck!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Did you have to tune any parameters or something, or did you just turn.
Kostadis Roussos: No, dude, I haven't even gotten to that phase yet.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So you're tuning at the hardware level, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm just tuning at the hardware level so I can get adequate performance.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And not only tuning at the hardware level, tuning the configuration, right? Because the models, if you have to tell it, no, I don't want you to use the non-thinking variant. I want you to use the non-thinking variant. Oh, well, this model only goes into the non-thinking variant if you use this parameter that way.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, how… I don't know, but there are some platforms, like LM Studio and Olama, that.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so here's what happens. LM Studio and Olama are really good if you're not trying to do 200 requests per second.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I see, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: They, they…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: But the LM Studio has all of these, you know, controls, like, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: So, no, no, so let's be clear. If you have a GPU, right, and you can only install one model.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Olama… Olama's perfect.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, Olama is a platform, not the model I'm talking about.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, that's what I'm saying. I've used a Llama. I'm not saying this because I don't know what I'm talking about. I've, like, literally used a Llama. I set it up, I configured it, I tuned it. I spent a lot of time on it. The thing that a Llama buys you is that if you have a single GPU,
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And it's just you and your desktop, it's like the perfect solution.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I see. Okay, when there are multiple GPUs to run, like, you cannot actually use these to parallelize.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is this the same with LM Studio as well?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know about LM Studio. The other thing is that… the other thing that is, like, how do you handle the throughput? How do you send many, many requests to the GPU concurrently?
Kostadis Roussos: And I don't… Olama, up until very recently, didn't really have much support for that.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, right, yeah, yeah. Olama's was pretty basic, but I think LM Studio might have that, because I remember adjusting the thinking and the temperature.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, so adjusting thinking and temperature is not the part they don't have. Sorry, that… the part they don't have is the ability to.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Run on multiple GPUs.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no. Handle multiple concurrent requests, and use the KV cache efficiently.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Where VLLM does is it basically pre-allocates a large chunk of memory.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, I mean, let's be clear, what does it do? You may have heard of this thing called a page table.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. So, basically, what GPUs are doing is reinventing everything we knew about operating systems all over again.
Kostadis Roussos: Just calling them different words.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, right, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, the memory bus is renamed to, like, NVLink or something, like… Right, right, right.
Kostadis Roussos: And so the GPU… so the KV cache is essentially pages.
Kostadis Roussos: In memory.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And so what happens is that when you're allocating… when it's doing… it's creating KV key-value pairs that it wants to reuse… that it may want to use later, it needs to allocate those in memory. And if you don't have a contiguous chunk of memory, you can end up with lots of memory fragmentation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, which will slow down the things.
Kostadis Roussos: will slow down the performance, and it'll get, you know, all the bad things that happen, right? And so what VLLM does is it knows how to handle the memory so that if you're starting multiple jobs at the same time on the same GPU, you don't get memory fragmentation, you get KV cache reuse, you get a whole bunch of nice… because it basically builds
Kostadis Roussos: A virtual memory subsystem.
Kostadis Roussos: effect… at a conceptual level, right? Obviously, it's not… which knows to go, okay, if you want this KV, you want to go to that physical memory location, rather than, you know, the OLAMA, which basically will start allocating KV cache left, right, and center.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Got it, okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so if you want to do things at that, with higher throughput and higher performance, you need to go to those techniques. But they have a different problem, which is the VLLMs.
Kostadis Roussos: Require pre-allocated memory.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We are not required for pre-allocated.
Kostadis Roussos: The VLLM…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: To load the weights, right?
Kostadis Roussos: No, to load the K… for the KV cache.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: For the KV cache. And what does the KV cache have? Like, the input context?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, what is the KV cache? Now you're asking me, what is KVCache? And now I have to…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm not asking what a KV cache is, but what does it store? Like, why does it need to be filled up?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on. The problem is that I know this, and then I forget it. So let me just… and since you asked, and I want to know it again, you're now… I'm now going to look it up. You're gonna have to, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And in Transform LLMs, every token attends to every previous token via tension.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: During inference, the KV cache grows as the sequence lengthens. Each new token appends its KV pair to the cache.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so the cache is GPU VRAM. It's often the bottleneck for running long your… are often about how much KV cache VRAM as compute?
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: So it's basically how many of these things you can keep in memory.
Kostadis Roussos: And so if you're trying to run a system, if you're… if you're… the problem is that if it's only one app person using it, one prompt at a time, you're not getting a lot of thrashing and…
Kostadis Roussos: And memory fragmentation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: But if you've got 10 requests going to the same GPU, there's fragmentation. So, like, VLLM and KVCache, that's kind of where it became famous. Let me just get you that information.
Kostadis Roussos: Is paged attention, a way to maintenance KV cache memory the way an OS manages virtual memory. Before VLLM, KV cache was allocated as one contiguous block per request, sized to the maximum possible sequence list. This wastes memory two ways, internal fragmentation, external fragmentation.
Kostadis Roussos: With many concurrent requests, this made GPU memory utilization terrible, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: splits the KV cache into fixed-sized pages. Pages are allocated on-demand as the sequence grows, not up front. As requests KV cache can be spread across non-contiguous pages, just like virtual memory on disk.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? I mean, like, literally, it's your page subsystem.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, that's pretty much, like, page generation.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so, yeah, so VLLMs added that feature.
Kostadis Roussos: So it enables much larger batches.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: platform. I've not heard of the VLLM before.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah, it's a platform.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Got it.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, enables KV cache sharing. If two requests share a common prefix, they can literally share the same physical pages.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so if you want to drive higher concurrency, this starts to matter.
Kostadis Roussos: Got it.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What was.
Kostadis Roussos: the other thing you said? LLM Studio?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: LM Studio, just LM.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I'm just curious. LM Studio versus KVCAB versus the LLM.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just see what it says. I will read it, and I will tell you what I know is factual versus hallucinations from… It's really funny to see how they hallucinate about themselves. You know one of the funniest things to do?
Kostadis Roussos: Is to ask a question of Gemini… of Claude. Shove it into Gemini, get Gemini's response, and then shove it into Claude.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I remember you did that.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: last month. Yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I mean, like, I've seen videos where, you know, they put up Siri against the Samsung Bixby or other personal assistant, like, you know, the voice.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: agents talking to them, talking to each other, but I've not seen… The 9th time.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so basically, okay, so it's got lower throughput, because it doesn't have the paged-in attention continuous matching.
Kostadis Roussos: The LM Studio is easier to use, it's adequate.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Not for production, I just say.
Kostadis Roussos: adequate for production, model behavior, quantization, it's… you know, it's a fun thing to play, but, like, if I just tried to convert, like, I just tried to do a whole bunch of things with, like, 20 million tokens, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, okay, yeah, your scale is, like, pretty big, so… So, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so that's, like, I mean, you know, I was doing it 200 tokens per second, what, you have this look on your face.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, no, no, I was… I was just thinking, like, no, I misunderstood the DGXpark to be, like, a supercomputer, which can run
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I thought you were running Linux and maybe installed this, but VLLM seems to be the right choice for that kind of hardware.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Seville, yeah, Seville, so just so you know, what is a DGX Spark? It's a Blackwell.
Kostadis Roussos: with an ARM processor, 128GB of unified memory.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And so you can use that memory for the GPU or for the CPU.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And so what I discovered was my damn thing was crashing because the CPU was being starved of memory.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, yeah, that happens, I mean.
Kostadis Roussos: Where I'm just trying to tell you, like, the things I was debugging. I was like, seriously?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And why was it starved, the CPU?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, because what happened was that…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, because I just configured it poorly.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? I just can… what hap- okay, no, no, no, no, here's what happened.
Kostadis Roussos: As… so when you're… when you're sending many, many requests, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Ray and VLLM have code that parses those requests.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Correct.
Kostadis Roussos: And so, as it parses more and more requests, it needs more and more memory to parse the requests.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is it because all of them are stored in memory? Like, the pages, the pagination?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, no, no, let me give… let me… No, like, it doesn't have…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: To all the richness need nodes.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you need…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: you stored in the memory, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, hold on, I'll, I'll, I'll… I just got that research here today.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so, basically, so the thing is that…
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, I think it… I'm not entirely convinced I… what happened was Ray was crashing, let me just phrase it that way.
Kostadis Roussos: as Ray was using more and more memory, and as it was using more and more memory, it caused the system to start swapping.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I have a very stupid question. What is a rate?
Kostadis Roussos: I'll answer that in a second.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, radar.io.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Scale machine gun.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's an AI computer.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Why did I not hear about any of this?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, one, because race bonds one worker per process, per CPU core by default. Each worker has its own Python interpreter.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's very overkill, like, super overkill, I mean.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, well, you asked, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, okay, yes, yes, I understood, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, it allocates a shared memory object store. By default, 30% of total system RAM.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So it's the orchestration layer, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: AI Compute Engine.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: To solve, support any, we irritable.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, so anyway, so yeah, so those are… so those are some of the parameters you have to… to use. But it's kind of funny, like, I'm not using these things, and I'm going… I'm beginning to understand.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, this shit is not trivial to make work.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: That's my, like, wow, this is, like… My reaction, right?
Kostadis Roussos: How hard could it possibly be?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I did not do it at your scale with the DJX Park, but I got an old, Surface Book.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Which had NVIDIA GPUs, and installed this LM Studio, and I was trying to run a model. My god, it was, like, hogging, like, so much. It was not able to use the GPUs, unfortunately. I don't know why I need to debug that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Okay, let's play. Let's play. Anyway, I just… this was a fun conversation, and I…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, I mean, like, it is super difficult. I don't understand, you know, why people think AI is already there and jumping to self-driving cars and robots. They have a lot of shit to figure out here.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my god, I know, I was like…
Kostadis Roussos: I'm like, are you people serious?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, let's start.
Kostadis Roussos: That's fine. Okay, let me go to zoom.
Kostadis Roussos: Hey, do you have any recommendations for an Indian place in South Bay?
Kostadis Roussos: In Sunnyvale?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Indian restaurant.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, for me to order takeout.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Takeout, working, like, pan or rice.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: I eat everything, so… just tell me your recommendation. Where would you go eat? Where would you go grab food?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: When I was in Sunnyvale, let me think…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, I know a couple of restaurants, but, you know, the quality has dropped now, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, fine. So, no, no, I do not want your opinion, then. You give it… I got your answer. The quality has dropped. Therefore, I do not want your food.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, no, no. The restaurants, I know the quality have dropped, but there are better restaurants. Let me search.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I can remember that.
Kostadis Roussos: Mom's biryani?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, no, I don't think that's an actual restaurant, that is, like, a cloud.
Kostadis Roussos: Kebab and curry? That one's a good one.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, yes, kebab and curry.
Kostadis Roussos: That's… that's the one I'm getting from. I made up my mind. I have… I like that place a lot, and I had forgot… I had forgotten about it.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let's go tandoori chicken leg.
Kostadis Roussos: What is wash and spicy?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Wait, is that the Santa Clara thing?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, that's a… that's a… yeah. But that's not… Yeah, no, it's the same.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, what?
Kostadis Roussos: I know it's Pakistani, I'm aware, I'm aware… I know, I know what it is. It's a Pakistani place.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I've been there once.
Kostadis Roussos: You've only been there once?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Only once, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, do you want to hear something funny?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I was at,
Kostadis Roussos: When I was in my, many years ago, when I… people always could never get my name right, right?
Kostadis Roussos: And so, I can't…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is this the Kuldeep thing that you're gonna.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, Kuldeep, yeah, so this… but this is where… no, no, no, no, this is not Kuldeep. Okay. This is… so, I was get… got really annoyed that people couldn't remember my name, and so I would say, my name is Stan, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Stan, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And then people would get my name confused. Because by the time I start… after a while, people started getting my name confused, because Indians didn't… for Indians, the name Stan is as strange as Custatus.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And so I got… so I decided, screw this, you know, embrace… embrace the… embrace the market you're in, so I started using the name Kartik.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Got it? Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, here's an important detail. First of all, I don't look like a Kartik. But secondly, Kartik, as you probably well know, is typically the name of a very high-caste Indian.
Kostadis Roussos: Who's a vegetarian?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Mostly, I guess.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, most likely gonna be a vegetarian.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I called up and ordered food from this restaurant full of meat, and they asked me, what's your name? I said, Kartik.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And the guy basically goes, You're a Karthik?
Kostadis Roussos: The next time I go there, and I was like, there was a guy, and he was like.
Kostadis Roussos: He starts asking me, like, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: questions that, like, he looks at me, and he kind of gives me this look of, are you? Who are you? I go, card ticket. He kind of gave me that same look of, like…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I agree.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, why is this Kartik… who is this Kartik, and why is he eating, you know.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Meat.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. I was like, okay, fine, you know what, you guys can't deal with this, that's your problem, you know, I'm not gonna live in your cultural challenges.
Kostadis Roussos: And then one day, I'm just thinking, I'm just kind of embracing it.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Until one day, I go to the restaurant, and the guy goes, what's your name? Kartik. He goes, is that K-A-R-T-H-I-K, or K-A-R-T-I-K-H? And I'm like, screw this shit! My name's Gustavius!
Kostadis Roussos: You know.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Just for the record, the second spelling he told you is actually wrong.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just telling him what he said, alright?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, I understood.
Kostadis Roussos: By the way, I have friends of mine who spell it that way.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, really? Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Kostadis Roussos: No, I have friends who spell it that way, so…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, you know, this is funny, because this reminds me of that CAPTCHA check. Wait, are you a human?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: a secondary check.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I actually wanted to ask you the spelling and check the.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm like, do you really need my fucking name?
Kostadis Roussos: And that's when I… that's when I gave up.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I sent you a recommendation, like, that is pretty good.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: They just opened, like, Last month, or the month before.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, well, I'm gonna go… I haven't had this… I haven't had these guys in ages, so… and I really like them, so I'm gonna go with this. Okay, cool. But I will keep your recommendations. Did you put… send it to me in the chat… in the Discord?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, no, I, I… yeah, I'll send it to Industry.
Kostadis Roussos: No, if you sent it via… you did not put it in Zoom, is what I'm asking.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, not in the Zoom, I sent on my iMessages.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, great, that's fine. Great. I just, because zoom, I'm gonna lo- lose. Alright. Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: This is Dungeons & Dragons. Nobody plays Dungeons & Dragons. They start playing, and then they spend 2 hours talking about everything else. Alright, okay, roll 20.
Kostadis Roussos: This is what happens when I don't have my wife telling me I have to get onto the rest of my day.
Kostadis Roussos: I goof off.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Are they traveling over?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, they're up in the cabin.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Cabin?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah, I have a cabin up in the Barrier, in the Bear Valley.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Beverly Hills.
Kostadis Roussos: Bear Valley, it's a mountain, it's a… it's, if you know where Tahoe is, it's 50 miles as the crow flies from Tahoe.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, maybe a metaphor, okay, let's go.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Okay. So, our, our friends, our adventurers, our heroic adventurers, had just finished defeating the, the, had just cleared out the Cragmaw Hideout. They had collected some, some goods.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. For, Linene Graywind, who, who works in… who is running the Lionshield coster full of goods and materials.
Kostadis Roussos: That they could return as a reward.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? They also had Sildar, who was very happy to see them, and was willing to give them 50 gold pieces if they would just, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Take him to town.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Now, as in, back to, vandalin.
Kostadis Roussos: Phandalin.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Phandalin, okay, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Sildar wants to go find… and you also found out that Sildar is a member of the Lord's Alliance.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And as we discussed, the Lord's Alliance is one of the many factions in this world.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Power, you know, protector.
Kostadis Roussos: The Lords Alliance are the group… is the faction that's committed to centralized power.
Kostadis Roussos: to state power. The Harpers are the ones that are committed to decentralized power.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: They are aligned… they are not aligned. The Emerald Enclave towards the forests, the Order of the Gauntlet, all is good, the Zhentarim trade is the only thing that matters.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Right. And as always, I have to remind you that in my campaigns, factions have factions.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Factions? I have factions?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Much like in a company, not everybody is aligned. In my campaigns… Oh, okay. Not everybody… not every… Factions have factions.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, that example is a spot answer, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you arrive in Phandalin. Alright, let's go to Phandalin. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you should be able to hear music, I hope.
Kostadis Roussos: If you're… if you got the Cern Skip page, you should be hearing music now.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I am on that page.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you hear this?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Let me click the link that you sent again.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll also check the volume.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, can you play it now?
Kostadis Roussos: Also, I'll give you another… I'll just drop another link inside here, maybe that link died for whatever reason.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you hear anything?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, that worked.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Can you hear now?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I think…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Hear all the birds.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, cool. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Cheers.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: What fun?
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Oh, I know why I was not hearing it, I was using a different audio setup. Alright, okay. Alright, so you arrived into Phandalin. By the way, if you… and you just… if the noise gets too loud for you, just adjust your own volume, right? So don't…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so just… if you don't want to hear the music, just turn it off. This is… it amuses me, so I like to listen to the music. If it bothers you. If it bothers you, feel free to turn it off.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you're back in… you're back in… in Phandalin, and I'm actually… let me just… you're arriving… you're coming in from the north.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see… Nice party.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you're arriving from the north.
Kostadis Roussos: Sildar… let me just make sure what Sildar wants to do… I took notes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, as you… so you're arriving sort of in the late afternoon. I mean, it is a… it was a late evening. The stores are mostly closed, but the Stonehill Inn is still open, so you might want to head out there to grab… to grab some food and… and some sleep.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Here's Sildar. Alright, so you should, you should see Sildar, you should see a Sildar icon. Yes?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me make sure you can see his name…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you should be able to see his name. Do you see his name?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I see.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, you arrive, Sildar is like, I'm tired, I wanna go, go to catch some Zs. I don't know about the rest of you. Shall we?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let's hand it out, send it.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you guys can go do something else, but it's… I'm just saying, what he wants to do is to go catch some Zs.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, okay, so, I mean, so we'll spend some time in the Stonehill Inn Tavern.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: See what, the folks have got to say.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, maybe.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I was expecting a hero's welcome, but no.
Kostadis Roussos: No heroes welcome? Is that, is that what you're saying?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, I was expecting… maybe inside the Stonehill Tavern, I might.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you were expecting a hero's welcome, is that what I'm hearing, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Correct.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is that part of the plan, or no?
Kostadis Roussos: You were expecting a hero's welcome, dude?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, right now.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, I can eat goblins, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Like, he's like, I killed goblins, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, hold on.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, maybe, maybe this is the character of the…
Kostadis Roussos: Cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you tell that to Pip, right? Like…
Kostadis Roussos: Pip's like, you know, the thing about being a hero…
Kostadis Roussos: The thing about being a hero, buddy is that heroes…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that's a much more reasonably sized tavern. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Even… that's a little bit too big. Yes. Okay, there we go.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you arrive at the tavern.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, there's tuck.
Kostadis Roussos: There's Elsa, who's a barkeep.
Kostadis Roussos: There's Frida, who's one of the locals. There's Narth, who's another local. Apparently, people don't have anything better to do all day.
Kostadis Roussos: There's Toblen.
Kostadis Roussos: And let's get Sildar.
Kostadis Roussos: And sold our… And let's put you… okay. So you should now see yourself in the inn, yes?
Kostadis Roussos: Which is now scaled appropriately.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: He, when he looks at you, he's… Toblen says… he… Toblen meets you out the door, alright? So…
Kostadis Roussos: And so as you, as you're pulling up to the, inn complaining about, you know, how nobody loves you, and everybody's, nobody cares about you, Toblen runs out and says, Well, I'll be darned!
Kostadis Roussos: You, you brought him, he, he's alive! I didn't think anyone had… I didn't, I didn't, I didn't ask anyone for the odds, but, but good, come in, come in, whatever you need!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: It's filling with pride.
Kostadis Roussos: What? And tucks, like, you found him! You found him! He didn't disappear! And he runs up and gives you a hug.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: As promised, kid.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: I'd promise you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Promised kid. I brought him back.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, and he goes, you're so good! You're so good, blah blah blah blah blah! You're so good! You're so good!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And he just swells with pride.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip's like, you know, kid, it was a team sport.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Neat.
Kostadis Roussos: I think something better.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Burning, some, some components.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you gonna, like, share the credit, or are you gonna take it all?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, I'll, yeah, it's all teamwork.
Kostadis Roussos: Gig, so…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Everybody contributed.
Kostadis Roussos: Everybody contributed? Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I just need to do something. Alright. So he goes, so, Sildar turns to you and says, I'd buy you a drink, but I'd suspect I'd fall asleep into it. Tomorrow, I owe you a proper conversation, a proper drink, and a proper fee.
Kostadis Roussos: And so he declares that he'll pay you tomorrow morning, and he goes off to sleep. What?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, are we gonna stand here all day, or are we gonna go inside and have a…
Kostadis Roussos: You go inside to have a drink, I presume, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes. No, this is my dialogue to the top left.
Kostadis Roussos: Toblen says, oh, well, come in, come in, whatever you need! Like, I mean, you're the heroes of the hour!
Kostadis Roussos: When you walk in, the locals kind of raise an eyebrow and go, well, well, well, you managed to, that you managed to save some people.
Kostadis Roussos: The old lady, who was grouchy about the Redbrand says, well, it's good that you brought Sildar, but did you deal with the Redbrands yet?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, nothing at all, we found where it's impact.
Kostadis Roussos: One of the other guys says, well, were these goblins at all related to the Redbrands?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: How do you know if goblins are related to parent brands?
Kostadis Roussos: well, the Redbrands are a gang, and you do know that when you said, I'm glass, you know, Glasstaff, they attacked you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah, I remember that, yes, yes. Okay, yeah, I, I, yes, they, they most likely are related to the Redbrand, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Really?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: How do you know?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We, we came across, A bugbear.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And, and we managed to kill it.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh!
Kostadis Roussos: So, there was a bugbear running some goblins and ambushing people along the road. Did you hear anything else? Anything else of any note?
Kostadis Roussos: So, just to remind yourself, you heard about the weird goblin from, Sildar.
Kostadis Roussos: Who said the weird name?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yo.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: There was a goblin that Sildar was mentioning, but I need to talk to him.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: a little more tomorrow when he's awake. He's pretty tired, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Weird.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, so far, I would say, like, we had a pretty good run, and… the…
Kostadis Roussos: We're the heroes. Elsa, Elsa says, well, I know when my sister comes, she's gonna be an even bigger hero than you, but by golly, here's some ale for saving one of our own. And she pours out some beer, and for getting rid of those goblin bandits.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Thank you, Elsa.
Kostadis Roussos: Cheers.
Kostadis Roussos: Cheers. Cheers to everyone.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Let's, let's drink.
Kostadis Roussos: And celebrate tonight.
Kostadis Roussos: Get back to the adventure tomorrow.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Thank you for all your support and the information that you guys gave.
Kostadis Roussos: That was helpful.
Kostadis Roussos: It was all… it was helpful?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you guys head off to sleep.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, take a long rest, adjust your hit points accordingly.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Points… yeah, there are 16.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, you want to hit the long rest button, because it resets a whole bunch of things.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Recur half hit days, recur all hit dice. You know, one is the 5e rule, and the other is the 5.5.
Kostadis Roussos: 5.5, 5.5.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Thanks for happening.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, fine.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Long little speaker.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: We learned a little piece, huh.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, everybody's, done that?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Sue… In the morning…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, in the morning…
Kostadis Roussos: Let's go, I need to do something… this is what happens when you have too many notes.
Kostadis Roussos: You're like, hold on, I have a plan.
Kostadis Roussos: It's like, people are like, this is what ruined Dungeons & Dragons. Too much preparation, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I hope something ominous does not happen.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: While you're… while… so in the morning, as you're having… you come down for breakfast, right?
Kostadis Roussos: And, in addition to, you know, and there's a… There is a…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, and there is an additional NPC.
Kostadis Roussos: Additional character.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Sildar is, is there, and as is,
Kostadis Roussos: Background.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Sildar is there, he sees you and says, Welcome! Welcome! Welcome! Come, come, come, let's have some breakfast!
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Let's go there.
Kostadis Roussos: So you, so while you're sitting there, you also notice
Kostadis Roussos: A guy who's, like, drinking beer really early in the morning.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, fine. Right?
Kostadis Roussos: But, okay, roll a insight check, or an investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you roll?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: One sec.
Kostadis Roussos: Nope.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, let me share my screen before that.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, go for it.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: He, he would see this, decision?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, so hit click OK.
Kostadis Roussos: Go to the Features and Traits part of your character sheet.
Kostadis Roussos: There, that's it.
Kostadis Roussos: So what happens, okay, so with the JavaScript… so this, this, this, this, beyond D20 basically reads your local JavaScript.
Kostadis Roussos: Cash.
Kostadis Roussos: And so, that… what happens is the web page only refreshes the cache when you go to the features and traits page.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I see, okay, okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, it needs you to go to the features and traits page so that the thing downloads it, so that's what it's telling you, just go there so it could refresh.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I went there, I think it was there.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it refreshed. That's exactly what it was doing. Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: The role in investigation,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so actually, I'm sorry, I wasn't drinking. He's, he's, I got my timelines confused. He's, he's eating breakfast.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? He's dressed like a laborer.
Kostadis Roussos: And, he's kind of like…
Kostadis Roussos: He's got, like, he's a man, he's a man, like, having breakfast.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Rolling an investigation check.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, would you roll?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: It says a B.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't repeat.
Kostadis Roussos: No, you couldn't have rolled the B.
Kostadis Roussos: You rolled a 24.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, it said B, on the.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, B, oh, no, B is, means a natural 20. Sorry.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Summit 20.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Weird.
Kostadis Roussos: You notice that as Toblen comes… passes by, he's got a weird look on his face, as if whoever that person is, is somebody dangerous.
Kostadis Roussos: Your instincts go that this might be somebody who works For, what?
Kostadis Roussos: Might be somebody who's working for the Redbrands.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, alright. So as you sit down, he, he sits down…
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, ha-hem. So! I, you know, it's, I know that my, my poor friend…
Kostadis Roussos: My poor friend, Gundren was taken.
Kostadis Roussos: And.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Speaking to whom? Toblen, or Mike?
Kostadis Roussos: No, to you guys, you guys… I'm assuming… he's invited you to have breakfast with him, so I'm assuming you're gonna go sit down and have breakfast with him?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, yeah, I'm gonna call him to our table, like, we are, like, five of us, why don't you come?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, he had a table that had enough space for 5 of you. It was almost as if he was preparing, like, so, sorry. You guys arrive in the morning, right? Sorry, let me just do this. You arrive in the morning, Sildar is already sitting there having breakfast.
Kostadis Roussos: The minute you walk in, he calls you to his table.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, so instead of going to Sildar, we…
Kostadis Roussos: So, do you want to go sit with them or not?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I want to sit with them, yes, we want to sit with you.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, you mean Sundar invited, to the table?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Wait, I'm confused. Who invited us to the table? The new guy, or the…
Kostadis Roussos: Sildar, Sildar.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just gonna put this guy's… give this guy, color, so that we can… we can refer to him. I'm gonna give him…
Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna give him the red color, since you think he's a red brat, alright? So…
Kostadis Roussos: As you passed by this guy, you noticed him give you a weird look, and you noticed Toblen had kind of gave an even weirder look.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So Sildar says, Sits down, sits down with you.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Sildar says, well…
Kostadis Roussos: As he sits down and says, This is a fine establishment, with excellent food and ale. I think you should definitely have the flapjacks.
Kostadis Roussos: they're…
Kostadis Roussos: Pancakes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: at the moment.
Kostadis Roussos: The pancakes, right? And so…
Kostadis Roussos: And he goes, I have to tell, he sits down and says, well, it's a good thing, it's a good thing Gundren hired you.
Kostadis Roussos: And it's… and he pauses and looks at you, goes, and I have to say that I didn't really think that, a rogue from the more disreputable parts of Neverwinter would be a man of his word and honor, but I guess I'm… I can always be surprised.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Bruh. Go back to bed.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Food?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, no, nothing, that actually didn't sound like a compliment.
Kostadis Roussos: I… I think it's… okay, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: You're quite correct, it actually didn't sound like a compliment.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: If you're wondering what it sounded like, it did not, right?
Kostadis Roussos: He says, so, but I must tell you what I have discovered.
Kostadis Roussos: Gundren… Gundren was taken specifically. It was not a random robbery. Someone told the goblins to grab Gundren and take the map.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the map to the Wave Echo Cave.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Work cave?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh!
Kostadis Roussos: So, the Wave Echo Cave is… is the cave… sorry, let me just remind you what the Wave Echo Cave is.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, no, no, I mean, I'm just playing along, you can.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you're playing along. No, I mean, he's the one who's the one who told you about the Pueve Echo Cave yesterday, remember? It's the cave that presumably is the mythical cave with lots of treasure that nobody's found and everybody thinks they're gonna go find?
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Here I will just… so that you don't… so that you know what it is.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just remind you…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, just to remind you…
Kostadis Roussos: Right. The three Rock Seeker's brothers, Gundren, Tharden, and Nundro, recently located an entrance, to the long-lost Wave Echo Cave, site of the minds of Phandelver Pact.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright? And just to remind you, the fan-to-lever packed.
Kostadis Roussos: Was that 500 years ago.
Kostadis Roussos: Clans of dwarves and gnomes made an agreement known as the Phandalin Pack, by which they would share a rich mine in a wondrous cavern known as the Wave Echo Cave.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, so this is the first time I'm hearing about the cave.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I think I told the two last time, but, well, we couldn't… Does the… the flip?
Kostadis Roussos: Here, I just put it in the, in the story notes so you have it.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, I may have forgot told it to you, I don't remember.
Kostadis Roussos: So, this is what you're told.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Because this is the first time I'm hearing about the final delivery package.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, okay, well then let me… then, hold on, or if this is the first time I will do it, then I… hold on, hold on, then I will, I will,
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: All just spills a lot came to the government.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, essentially, Sildar, reads this to you.
Kostadis Roussos: Who says this to you?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he goes… Well,
Kostadis Roussos: In addition to its mineral wealth, the mine contained great magical power. Human spellcasters allied themselves with dwarves and gnomes to channel and bind the energy into a great forge called the Forge of Spells, where magic could be crafted. Times were good, and the nearby town of Phandalin prospered as well, but disaster struck when bandits swept through the north and laid waste to all in their path.
Kostadis Roussos: A powerful bandit force was reinforced by evil mercenary wizards attacked Wave Echo Cave to seize its riches and magic treasures. Human wizards fought alongside their dwarf and gnome allies to defend the Forge of spells, and the ensuing spell battle destroyed much of the cavern.
Kostadis Roussos: Few survived the cave-ins and tremors, and knowledge of the location of Wave Echo Cave was lost. Four centuries, rumors of buried riches have attracted treasure seekers and opportunists.
Kostadis Roussos: to the area around Phandalin, but no one has located the lost mine. In recent years, the people resettled the area, and Phandalin is now a rough-and-tembled frontier town, but the Lord's Alliance is going to put an end to that, and bring it… bring order?
Kostadis Roussos: to this area.
Kostadis Roussos: And he pauses and goes, it's important to realize that Phandalin falls under the sway of his lordship, Lord Neverwinter.
Kostadis Roussos: And is recognized by the Lord's Alliance as part of the broader area under the Lord Neverwinter's protection.
Kostadis Roussos: And any treasure that was found in the Wave Erico Cave fundamentally belongs to his lordship and the City of Neverwinter.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Interesting.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just… Yes, sir.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Guys?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: But that was a very good deal.
Kostadis Roussos: Then he goes, Recently, a trio of dwarves, the Rockseeker brothers, whom you met the oldest, discovered… claim to have discovered the entrance to the Wave Echo Cave, and they intend to reopen the mines.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, unfortunately, they weren't the only ones interested in the wake of the Wave Echo Cave. A mysterious villain…
Kostadis Roussos: Who apparently controls a network of bandit gangs and goblins in the areas.
Kostadis Roussos: have followed the rock seekers to their prize, and that is why they captured Gundren Rockseeker.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Seeker, that's how he gets his name.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, no, he gets his day because he was born that way, his family, so it's an old Rockseeker.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Very, very, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Does he?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, Lord, Lord, rockseeker, right? No.
Kostadis Roussos: Gundren Rockseeker.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, no, not Gundren Rock Seeker, like, in the, in the fable, you mentioned,
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Lord of the Neverwinter.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Lord Neverwinter.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Never member. Okay, okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: say, Lord of Neverwinter if you can't remember her, or Neverwinter, if you can't.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Or, you know, you could say something obnoxious, because you're a rogue who was a thief in his city.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't have to call him. I mean, remember, you're a rogue, and he just called you. He just trashed you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't have to call them or never, you can call them whatever you want, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Probably not a good time to pick a fight with him, but yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, I'm just saying, you do not have to…
Kostadis Roussos: You do not have to be respectful and kind.
Kostadis Roussos: But there are consequences. Alright, so he then, he then continues, so that you now know the story, so he says, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And it was my intention to help Sir Gundren, my dear friend.
Kostadis Roussos: to secure the way of Echo Cave, for the benefit of the Lord's Alliance and Lord Neverwinter, and the City of Neverwinter. Of course, Gundren would have, as a member of society, had a contract to… what's the word I'm looking for? To,
Kostadis Roussos: was not… he would not be left unreumerated for his discovery, but he would be seen under the overall goal of protecting the interests and the concerns of the Lord's Alliance.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Everyone have anything to say to him?
Kostadis Roussos: Then he says, he goes, Now, I must say, I was not only traveling with Gundren, but I was also traveling to check on Iarno Albrek.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just gonna put… yeah, I'm about to put it in… in there.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: A wizard and old contact who had gone to Phandalin weeks ago and lured Alliance business and stopped sending reports?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so… is that it? And then he goes, can you look for Iarno?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Where was the last time you saw him post?
Kostadis Roussos: It goes… but before any… okay, so, pip… PIP kind of gives you a… A shove.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: A show?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. But before he gives you a shove, you realize Veyra, who's scribbling in her notes, says, it said Ruxithid, and I think it said Ruxithid, and you realize she's repeating the same name
Kostadis Roussos: That, of the, that the goblin said.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? The goblin with the strange face?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right.
Kostadis Roussos: She keeps saying, I think it said rixifit. Now, do you lick her, look at her, ignore her?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm like, I'll try to whisper to her, like, what are you doing? What are you writing?
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, well, I spent the entire evening re-reading my notes about the elongated headed goblin by candlelight.
Kostadis Roussos: And then… When I wrote it down, that phrase, elongated head goblin, My blue… Crystal flared.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: When you wrote the phrase.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, so, yeah, so Sister Maela goes like this, not this again.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And, and…
Kostadis Roussos: And Pip kind of goes,
Kostadis Roussos: Like, what do you do?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is Toblen with us?
Kostadis Roussos: Toblen is trying to be as far away from the commoner as possible.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay, so… oh, that way, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Not towards us.
Kostadis Roussos: No, he's definitely trying to, like, he's even moved behind the bar, and, like, he's trying to keep away from the commoner.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You definitely get the impression that Toblen does not want to be anywhere near that guy.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, how do you react to Veyra's, Veyra's comment?
Kostadis Roussos: Are you dismissive? Are you interested? Are you indifferent?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, I'm not dismissive about it, definitely, but,
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Well, did… I'm gonna ask to Veyra, like, well, did the candle glow when the goblin said that one?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, when I wrote the name down.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's what it will, but it's strange.
Kostadis Roussos: There… I'm telling you, there is something connected here.
Kostadis Roussos: And then she goes back to scribbling. Like, she… she… after doing that, she goes back to scribbling in her notebook, she's like, stop caring about you. She's like…
Kostadis Roussos: Back, back to her, back to her notes. Back to making circles and arrows and flipping between pages.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Then I'm gonna leave her that way.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Before, I talk more, I wanna engage with, Sildar.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, but Pip, just before you engage with him, Pip goes, dude, I don't mean to be rude about this, but, like, when somebody says, can you go look for someone, the first words out of your mouth should be, how much?
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, Pip goes, I don't… I'm like, I'm all about doing the good deeds, but, like, we also need to eat.
Kostadis Roussos: And he also owes us 50 gold pieces. Plus he turns… plus he's a member of the Lord's Alliance. Those guys are, like, swimming in cash. We should, like, get some money here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Totally agree, but yeah, I need to clarify a few things before…
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just picking up at it.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: committees.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: You're free to, you know, ask him for the money and, you know, volunteer to bring up
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: bring that guy, Larno Albrek.
Kostadis Roussos: So, so he goes, so are you gonna volunteer, or are you gonna ask for money?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh no, I'm telling Pip.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That he's free to volunteer to go bring him up.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, Pip's saying, you're in charge, he's saying you gotta make sure to ask for money.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't just volunteer to do things, man. Like, ask for money!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, so… Yeah, I'm gonna ask Sildar, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Remember, he also hasn't paid you for the 50 gold pieces he's supposed to owe you, just keep that in mind.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I don't know.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, I… okay, the 50 is different from the initial 30 that I got, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. He paid you 50 to bring you here. Apparently, the guy is swimming in enough gold that he gave you 50 gold to do a safe walk.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And he's definitely given the impression that this is, you know, as you look at his clothes, he does not strike you as the impoverished type.
Kostadis Roussos: Plus, you did meet him in a fancy bar… tavern in Neverwinter.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Fair point.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, yeah, I'm gonna ask him, like, how long do you know this guy.
Kostadis Roussos: Iarno?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'll break.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he goes, how long have I known him?
Kostadis Roussos: Well… Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Quite some time.
Kostadis Roussos: I doubt not on a personal level, but as a member of the Lord's Alliance, I knew him.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, he is in Europe a lot of airlines.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, well, he was my agent. I'm sorry, did I not mention that? Yes, he was an agent of mine.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And you haven't heard from him since how long?
Kostadis Roussos: 4… Boom!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Here's what it's.
Kostadis Roussos: Weeks.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Sweet.
Kostadis Roussos: He was an old contact who had gone to Phandalin weeks ago on Lord's Alliance Business and stopped sending reports.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I can, I can find him for you, but 18?
Kostadis Roussos: That could…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: be risky, and I'm…
Kostadis Roussos: you know, putting my life at line, so… Well, I…
Kostadis Roussos: You know, it says, you know, he says, Iarno and I have known each other for many years. We weren't… we weren't friends. I mean, you know, he was… he was a professional friend, not one that I… that we invited to each other's families and dinners, but, you know, I… I did, he says, I did recommend him for the Phandalin constabulari assignment.
Kostadis Roussos: That was as an agent of…
Kostadis Roussos: You know what a constable is?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Constable, yeah, yeah, the police.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I did recommend him for the constable area assignment here. We're not close friends, but, you know, we are well known, and I'd like to think that I was a bit of a mentor for him, and a friend.
Kostadis Roussos: On a professional level, I mean, our families didn't mix very much in society, but that's not… that wasn't to be expected. Roll a perception, roll an insight check.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, he's not… are you saying that he's not important?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, what you… you're a member of Neverwinter, and you know what that really means. It means that they were different social classes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Always yield.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, la-la-la.
Kostadis Roussos: I think that when you, when you're…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, you got that, like, I'm just saying, like, since you're from Neverwinter… Yeah, you immediately realize, oh, shit, these guys… in Neverwinter, there's, like, a lot of status symbol amongst the powerful and the elites.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, he's an agent of the… of this guy, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, they're all part of the Lord's Alliance, but Sildar thinks he's better than him.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, perfect, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. But he's, like, thinks that he's also helped Iarno, and so… and he feels responsible for Iarno, in a kind of noblesse de blige, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, okay, so perception?
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: He then says, and the other thing I want you to do, if you don't mind,
Kostadis Roussos: Find out who the Black Spider is!
Kostadis Roussos: And find out why Gundren has gone missing.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Wow. You would fill me a bunch of tasks at the same time, and you still didn't have… haven't answered my question.
Kostadis Roussos: Well… Oh, well, there you go. Well, first of all, you're getting the 50 gold pieces for, bringing…
Kostadis Roussos: For bringing, for bringing me hears safely, so he gives you the 50 gold.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And then he says, and there'll be another 200 gold pieces if you find him and bring him back safely.
Kostadis Roussos: Y'all know safely.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Iarno?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. And he pauses and says, and I do want to say something else.
Kostadis Roussos: It is the interests of the Lord's Alliance to discover who the Black Spider is, and I think that you owe a certain amount of personal loyalty to go find Gundren.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Can you elaborate a little bit on how I want to personally, you know, how am I personally loyal to Gundren?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm, you know, this is me talking, like, you know, trying to…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you're basically… he goes, well, he pauses, he goes, perhaps there's no personal loyalty, but the Lord's Alliance would look very favorably
Kostadis Roussos: On someone who brought the Black Spider to justice and rescued Gundren?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, so, with all due respect, like, this is what I think. See, when you hire… when Gundren hired me initially, like, he did not tell me how dangerous this journey was going to be, and I've almost put my life online, like, multiple times, like, to save you, to…
Kostadis Roussos: The goblins attacked our, you know, For the goods. So, Okay?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: This is going to be more than 200, I would need… I would be needing, like, 500 to bring Gardner back.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he goes, no, no, he goes, that's highway robbery.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's definitely, you know, I…
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just telling… 500 gold pieces is a mythical sub.
Kostadis Roussos: Is a mythical sum.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, 250, 300 gold… 300 gold pieces is a… is…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's a lot.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, 500 gold pieces is a shit ton of money.
Kostadis Roussos: He, like, would la- it's kind of like, you know, 200 gold pieces is already a lot of money.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Settle at 300.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: $300, and you, you pay me, like, $150 upfront right now.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Half of it up front, and half after I finish the job, and let's…
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you and goes, You, sir, drive a very hard bargain. And he smiles.
Kostadis Roussos: 50 up front, 250 when you bring… when you comp… 50 up front, 150 when you bring Iarno, and 100 for Gundren.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, no, no.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: London was not part of this deal before, so I'll take $100 upfront and the 200 when I bring Iarno back.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Otherwise, you can find someone else.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Because my job ends with delivering the goods.
Kostadis Roussos: He, he, he…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I also need to find who the Black Spider is, and also bring Gundren back, so there are a lot of things for me to do.
Kostadis Roussos: It's about pri-Pip goes, as the man said, it's about priorities.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, Pip's very pleased with you. He's, like, he's, like, going… he's, like, he's, like, kind of really happy, like, you're standing up to this, this, this pompous bully. Sildar sighs and hands over, like, 100 gold.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 100 GP.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so the next thing you need to go to is the Lion Shield Coaster to give the goods back.
Kostadis Roussos: Board.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I've already given him the bathrooms promotion.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, but remember you found the goods in the, the… The cave?
Kostadis Roussos: That belonged to the Lion Shield Coaster.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I… okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. If you look at last week's notes.
Kostadis Roussos: Such that they are.
Kostadis Roussos: You, you had, returned, some, you, you had found some of her missing goods in… among the stuff that the, the, the, the bandits had stolen.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you remember that at all? Or did you read… did you read up on it?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, I'm looking…
Kostadis Roussos: Let me stop, just let me… hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, I know what, I know what, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so this was… unfortunately, I did not do a recording, so I am going to… we have to resort to the Zoom summary.
Kostadis Roussos: So, if you… I just updated the notes there.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, okay, it's just not clear.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, do you remember it now? I'm sorry.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I recall it now, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: She'll get the goods, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: That would be the one thing you need to do. The other thing… there are also some other quests you can have. The other thing is there's this guy who's looking at you, and so you could also…
Kostadis Roussos: Try to decide to see if you want to follow him and see where he goes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: He's leaving the town now?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I'm just saying he's still in the tavern. Like, he's slowly eating his porridge. Like, you've never seen somebody take so long to not eat his porridge.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: But yeah, I guess the goods can stay. That's not a priority, so I'll follow them.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean… okay, you're gonna follow him?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: By the way, did you order your food?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, my food just arrived, let me go get it. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: So my food did arrive.
Kostadis Roussos: I ordered a Franta Corma, and
Kostadis Roussos: Kebabs. Tandoori and, she kebab.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, nice.
Kostadis Roussos: And,
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Solid from the office.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, good. Now, normally, I eat a salad, but my wife's out of town.
Kostadis Roussos: I was not at home, and she, like, only eats Indian from exactly one restaurant, which is a good restaurant, so I'm not complaining, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Like, it's my one day where I can eat Indian from not that place.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: So… I'm like, I, I like this place.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. We all have our preference. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, let me get something to drink.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: You wanna…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do you want to continue after we eat, or…
Kostadis Roussos: It's up to you. Do you want to, like, come back in, like, 20 minutes?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah, we can do that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I will just, pop… I'll stop the recording, we'll… I'll hang up, and we'll just ping me in 20 minutes, alright?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Or rather, if I get distracted, ping me in 20 minutes.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'll ping you in 20 minutes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I mean, if I… if I'm… I should be back here in 20 minutes, but as I've told you before, I get distracted. Okay. Just, like, don't, like… or call me, like, don't… don't worry, I just… there's nothing going on, it's literally I got distracted.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, yeah, 9th grade.
WEBVTT
Kostadis Roussos: I'm okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, righty.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's go…
Kostadis Roussos: I do not want that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you are still in the tavern.
Kostadis Roussos: But she step out the tavern. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: As you step out of the tavern.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, as you step… okay, so we step out of the… I'm gonna send him to the changelayer…
Kostadis Roussos: You step out of the tavern. Where do you want to go? To Barthen's prov… as you step… sorry, as you step out of the tavern,
Kostadis Roussos: The guy that you guys were… was following you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, I was following him.
Kostadis Roussos: You're following him, right? Yes. So, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So… I presume you're trying to be discreet?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I can roll the stealth.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Roll list it?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll, roll as you roll.
Kostadis Roussos: 4 plus 7, 11.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: So… As you get to over about here…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Maybe.
Kostadis Roussos: You notice… just make sure I got this right…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Another person?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Aye.
Kostadis Roussos: That's not the right one.
Kostadis Roussos: There we go. That's what I'm supposed to use.
Kostadis Roussos: Get some of the guys some excuse.
Kostadis Roussos: You realize that there's 4 guys, and they're kind of… Holding an ambush.
Kostadis Roussos: Shit.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? That you, you, you notice them, just rather roll your perception.
Kostadis Roussos: Exception.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, Insight Investigation, insider investigation, sorry, Insider Investigation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, okay, so, not a perception. Bad role, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: No, don't… ignore that. Roll your investigation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Investigations.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Stood by.
Kostadis Roussos: No, that's 23, man. That's very good. Yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I thought it was a 1.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it was about to be a 1.
Kostadis Roussos: 1 and 19 are on opposite sides.
Kostadis Roussos: No, 1 and 20 are on opposite sides, sorry. Alright, so, you see that there are four, there are four of these guys who are, sort of.
Kostadis Roussos: As you turn around the corner, you realize that there are 4 of them.
Kostadis Roussos: And the guy you were following… Is kinda just standing there.
Kostadis Roussos: And… looking around to see where you are.
Kostadis Roussos: Meanwhile, the rest of you, I presume, are sort of over here.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Okay, so…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: the car.
Kostadis Roussos: But…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right around the corner.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, right around the corner, so I'm assuming you're right around the corner. Alright, so Zenvon, do you want to, shout and tell your friends to attack? Do you want to go back? Like, they're obviously out to gang up on you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm gonna call my friends for help.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you wanna call… do you wanna… okay.
Kostadis Roussos: But I…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I need to, like, if they're not ready to engage, I'm gonna have to talk to them, like, who are you guys? Oh, that sounds like a good ambush.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, they clearly are looking to ambush you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Are they not gonna engage talking with me?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, so, so it's… so…
Kostadis Roussos: You could always, like, you know, Bravely and spectacularly say, Can't we just talk?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Well…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, this is, this is my response.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, I'm just gonna say, you can do that. He's the, like…
Kostadis Roussos: This guy sort of, like, is waiting for… to see if, like, the one guy who is… you were, who you were following is sort of waiting for you guys to… to follow… looks like he's looking for you guys to follow, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And he's kind of getting disappointed.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, okay, so when I noticed the ambush, I'm gonna ask him, so, looks like you were expecting me, like, are you not gonna introduce me to your friends?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, so that's your routine, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, that's my response, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, roll for initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: However, before you do that, roll an intimidation check.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Intimidations? Okay, interesting. Never done those.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I think it's the 19th.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see what happens.
Kostadis Roussos: Sweet.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is it to see that I'm intimidated, or the other person is.
Kostadis Roussos: No, did you intimidate him?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Perfect.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just do something…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So were we.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you tried to intimidate him.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh wait, would you try to intimidate him?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, I got a 20…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 19… no, I got 19…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so… He causes him to pause you for a second, he wasn't expecting you to… do that.
Kostadis Roussos: Huh.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: So, he's kind of like, he's got this look where he's trying to sense your motives, see what your plans are.
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, he's gonna see, wait for my plan to roll?
Kostadis Roussos: He's like, yeah, you kind of, like, he's not… he's paused, he wasn't expecting you to do that, so now… so now he's kind of like, okay…
Kostadis Roussos: What's your next move?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, I'll just tell them, let me bring some of my friends to introduce to you as well, and I'm gonna call them.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're gonna up the intimidation level.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Roll the implementation again, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you…
Kostadis Roussos: What did you get?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 1 and 13…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, if you're gonna introduce your friends, I'm gonna introduce MY friends! Get them, guys!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, it's gonna get messy. Fine.
Kostadis Roussos: It's gonna get messy.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, roll for initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: They're, they're, they're a gang, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And as far as they've concerned, they were running this town, and you've shown up, and are now gonna tell them who they can and can't do anything to?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, so these are the red brats.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: You could tell they're Redbrands because they've got red cloaks. Oh, I'm sorry, you didn't see the… sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you should… did you not see their names? No.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, there are no names.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, if I don't see names, just tell me, because I didn't notice that.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, so there's Redbrand Ruffian, Redbrand Ruffian.
Kostadis Roussos: 2… 3…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright? Yes, I see, yes. Alright, so they're very impressed with your balls.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: As they should be.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I'll… It's gonna roll an initiative check.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna get a generic battle map.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 9, 14.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm just gonna do something here.
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Kostadis Roussos: That's right.
Kostadis Roussos: That's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Let the… so the band… the bandits are sort of, like… Here.
Kostadis Roussos: You're sort of over here, and your guys are kind of over here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Can I move these characters a little bit?
Kostadis Roussos: Which ones? Yours? Yeah, you should be able to.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So… I'm thinking somewhere like this, and this guy… this guy was, like, 3 squares, I had 3 or 4 squares, because we were talking.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so he's right over here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, I see one guy in corner, that is fine.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you saw all 4 of them, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Correct, yes, yes. All three of them are in each corner, which is perfect. Okay, cool. Yeah, this is, this is more like it.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll for… why don't you roll for initiative?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I did, I got a 14.
Kostadis Roussos: You got a 14?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, 14.
Kostadis Roussos: I've got a 20, 20… About 19?
Kostadis Roussos: There, I've got the 8 plus 2.
Kostadis Roussos: 3… And this one… Plus 0, 14.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I forgot the question.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, this guy… Character sheet.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Only four, four in the turn order, or just the red one.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep. Yeah, there's only 4 Redbrands, yeah? Right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do we get an initiative turning? Like…
Kostadis Roussos: So, we all rolled for initiatives. Do you see the turn order?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I see only the Redbrands in the turn order.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you guys, you should… you're there, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, no, that's what I'm saying.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that's… I see what the problem is, my bad.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I, I, yeah, no wonder you're confused.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Zenvon had a 14, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I had 14 years.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Sister Maela… Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: I had a 19?
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra had a 4.
Kostadis Roussos: And, we'll just give her a 10.
Kostadis Roussos: Since I can't be bothered to… Alright, now you should see yourselves, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, good. Alright, so everybody good now?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Here.
Kostadis Roussos: The Redbrand ruffians.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: They look like Targaryens from Game of Thrones.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: They look like the Targaryens from the Game of Thrones, pictures with the blonde.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, yeah, they do, they don't that, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So,
Kostadis Roussos: No, he wouldn't do that. Alright, attacks Sister Maela with his short sword.
Kostadis Roussos: And does 4 points of damage.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: What does PIP do?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm assuming he's going to,
Kostadis Roussos: He's going to, attack… try to defend his… attack. Who do you want him to attack?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: The guy that's closer to him on the right side, like, on the bottom.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just give these guys numbers so that it's easier.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, which one? Do you want the one that says 1 or 2?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 2.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Pip's gonna go over here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Probably a good, good decision. Alright, roll, alright, roll to attack.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do I roll?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, you roll, dude, I'm like…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Poor him.
Kostadis Roussos: You can either roll on… you can either roll dice if you have dice, if not, I will… I will get you some dice, because it always brings me joy to buy dice for players.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, I don't have that. Wait, wait, hold on, I think I might have.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, dude, you just… or you can use the command line directly.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, one sec, please.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I have, I have this.
Kostadis Roussos: That's a… That's a DT, yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And I have this, that's a D…
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's a D10 as well.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's a detail note, and…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so just…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Ready.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, well, roll the 20.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll to hit.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 18?
Kostadis Roussos: That is a hit.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, you can use a hip.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, I will… you… the way… oh!
Kostadis Roussos: How much damage does he do?
Kostadis Roussos: He rolls a D8, so roll a D8. So the way you roll a D8 in… you can either go into D…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: These are the dies I have, so…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, but if you go, like, yeah, so to roll it electronically, you go into Roll20.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, R… Large date.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, D8.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Slash RD8, sorry, slash RD8.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. 4. Alright, so he also… but, he gets a strength bonus.
Kostadis Roussos: I know what it is, just hold on, I have to get it, I have to just,
Kostadis Roussos: His strength bonus is,
Kostadis Roussos: Plus 2, so he does 6 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Not bad.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: But then this other… this guy here goes, you arrogant… you think you're… you think you're so… tough, I'll show you what tough feels like.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And he, attacks you with a short sword.
Kostadis Roussos: And does 5 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, it's your turn.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I reduce my…
Kostadis Roussos: HP by 5.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, current night.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, I increased the damage to 5, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Your, your, yes, well, so it starts with your maximum, and you keep subtracting.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Correct, yeah, I mean, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you, did you mark it in your, your character sheet?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, so there are two ways. One is to…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you apply damage, and the others, you could do subtraction, yes, whatever, whatever works.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, yes, nothing. 5 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Turns out, cognitively, dissubtraction is hard for humans. Alright, Zenvon, you're up.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Now remember, you've got the NIC and the VEX option, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, Vex is, like, taking a… take a damage to it next attack goes against the creature.
Kostadis Roussos: So, so if you use Vex, your next attack can have a sneak attack bonus.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I'll do the NIC.
Kostadis Roussos: The Nick doesn't, but you can run away without being attacked.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I'm gonna run away.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, probably the right decision. Alright, so roll an attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, B20, right? I'll just do this.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Fix the cash flow.
Kostadis Roussos: So you can gr- you can click on the, the, the…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Like, on the…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Thank you, perfect.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: This one, no, wait, I'm gonna use the dagger, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so you first click on the daggers, so you see where… do you see all the way on the left? Here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: This one, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Click that.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do I have a disadvantage?
Kostadis Roussos: No, you don't have disadvantage. You only have disadvantage when you're in the dark. You don't have advantage. Does that make sense?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And that is a hit for 7 points of damage!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Thanks, cheers.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, do your second attack.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Second attack goes with.
Kostadis Roussos: Scimitar. Scimitar.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I guess.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see… Alright, that's another 7 points of damage. Damn!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, you must be bleeding.
Kostadis Roussos: The guy's, like, bleeding. Do you… and I presume you disengage and go towards your group?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I run back.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Sister Maela… Is she…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: take on this guy, right? There's one guy in the corner who has…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he hasn't, he hasn't attacked yet. Sister Maela looks at, the Redbrand Ruffian and says, I'll take care of him.
Kostadis Roussos: And she attempts to attack.
Kostadis Roussos: And she misses spectacularly. Alright, this Redbrand Ruffian attacks Thistle.
Kostadis Roussos: Not thistle, pit.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip's Armor Clause?
Kostadis Roussos: Oops, armor class is… what is his armor class? 16.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a 15, that is a miss.
Kostadis Roussos: And then, this guy… Charges… Straight over there.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Now it's Veyra's turn.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Nothing, kindly.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Veyra decides that, you know what, when in doubt, cast Magic Missile.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, see, it does… she kills this guy.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, wow, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he only had 2 hit points left.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Drops this guy by 4…
Kostadis Roussos: And drops this guy by 4.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: This Redbrand… Decides to attack Sister Maela again.
Kostadis Roussos: And he does 8 points of damage. She's hurting now.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just, she, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Right, okay. So, Pip, you're up. Pip's up. Roll for Pip's attack. Hold on. Before he does that, he's got a special ability.
Kostadis Roussos: No, you can't use it. Alright. Go for it.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I'm gonna do another time.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll a D20.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you hit! Alright, roll for damage. D… 8. Yep, D8 plus 2.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 3 points of time.
Kostadis Roussos: Not doing very well there, Pip.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 1 plus 2 is 3.
Kostadis Roussos: I think there's one more thing you can do, right? I don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, alright, Zenvon, you're up.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, Pip's up! Yeah, Zenvon, you're up.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so the, the, the guy who's… all of these guys can, can be used to,
Kostadis Roussos: You can have sneak attack bonus, so pick whoever you want.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Sneaked echo…
Kostadis Roussos: That gives, remember, 2D6 additional points of 2…
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so this is where, if you use VEX…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, sir. Okay, so you attack with your scimitar first.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, with an advantage, or just.
Kostadis Roussos: Normal, no advantage.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Which is the left one, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And the result is…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Scimitar to hit, 19 scimitar, 4 scimitar, Sneak Attack, and 4.
Kostadis Roussos: So, 8 points of dem… oh, hold on.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, 8.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you're a first level, sorry, you're not second, you're not third level, right? So, 8 points of damage. Well done!
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, now you have advantage with your second attack.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Second attack, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Shift, and then plus, and…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, oh yeah, I got a plus now, okay. I'll use the shorts for?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, with the… no, with the dagger.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Dang it.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Wait, why? Why cannot I use that?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, short swords, yeah, you could use the short sword, yeah, my bad. You couldn't use the short sword.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: incorrect.
Kostadis Roussos: 8.
Kostadis Roussos: 11 damage.
Kostadis Roussos: 11 damage?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yay.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, let me just see what this stupid meeting is.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I have a meeting now?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. I wanna see if I do.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 9.30.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to go to this meeting.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay, cool.
Kostadis Roussos: It was good hanging up, man.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, we'll catch up tomorrow.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, we will. This was, this was a little bit of a, little bit of a, A cliffhanger.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. Alright, take care. Take care, guys.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'll see you tomorrow, bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.